Hello friends, welcome to
our YouTube channel, Failed, let's start the two-week fast. The
first
question is, what should I do in Avantipur?
What can I buy at the current market price?
What can happen in July-August?
First, let's look at the chart.
We see two labels on the chart. One is the resistance of 520.
Earlier, this was support. As soon as
it broke, it became support and resistance.
Now you can see that
this return is visible from here.
Talking about support, there is support around 410.
Earlier also there was important resistance. Now we are
seeing it as important support.
And currently this stock is floating in the air. It is
neither above the resistance nor
around the support. There should be
no work at all right now. One should not think about July-August
right now. Once you get a perfect
entry, then you can buy. Either
it is halfway around the support, which is the level of 410,
so there can be work with a small stop loss
or else go above 520.
So we can work with a small stop loss here.
In the monthly chart of Nifty, RS10 is
moving in the negative zone. So, can we
see a cross here? First, let's
look at the monthly chart of Nifty-50. A
great rally was seen. After that,
in one channel, we see it trending and it is still
above its twenty-day moving average. In fact, it has not even touched it.
Minister RS10 is 67.5 even though
it is in the negative zone. But as long as Minister
RS10 is moving above the six-digit mark of any stock index, it
means that it is a long-term
police chart. There is
no need to worry about it. It has not even touched 30-digit level yet.
Look at this channel here, you cannot see it. It is
a little big here, but there is
no cross signal visible here. The
subscribe situation saw a huge decline,
but if we look at it, then we can see it.
Time is visible here
and it is good for us because
after so much movement, if this time correction happens then
After that, a breakdown requires a lot of patience.
Its maximum priority is that it will
go above from here. A breakdown will be seen.
You can see 1950 continuously going up.
This may take time. A
time correction of 2-3 months may be seen in two-three
months. And we are creating an address here,
but after that, the chances of a breakout are
high. The chances of a breakdown are very
low. You can see the data of 5. In
all the stocks, a similar pattern has been
seen here. A big rally came and
after that, if it is like this, then the
chances of a rally after that are high. If you
bought the stock at 5,000, then you should
average it now or else you should think
and give it a wave. So,
look at the chart. Currently, the chart is showing support of 4000
and the stock is trying to straighten at this level.
Do not sell it now due to its resistance around 4600. There are chances
that it can go above this level. A breakout can happen,
so you can place a position here at
3950.  If you look around or even look at the veins, there
is no issue right now and you
can say goodbye to it temporarily. If you
get the opportunity later, you can buy those. I will also
start wanting and you can stop
investing in states like which
platform to use which stock. So
look here, I have never
started investing in this stock directly. I have
not started yet. I
invest in this stock, but I was doing it through
mutual funds till now based on the history of NAC.
Now, I invest
here based on the history of NAC.
I believe that there are
many appointed leaders among the Indian leaders here
and they understand this market more or less well, so it will be
better if you invest here. And this will tell you
mine. Your decision may be different from this.
What is the exit level of Bandhan Bank
Iodine ₹10 for more than two years? Your
long term poem. So, if we talk about the chart,
technically, then it is the right time to
sell because it is trading at resistance.
It has topped out in the 330 to 350 zone many times and many times
you will see a decline from here. If
you have seen the stock continuously falling below this level, then if you
want to sell, you
can think about selling now. Otherwise, if you
want to fold for the long term, then place an order. There is no
doubt about it. But you
asked about the unification level, so according to me, it is
running at a good price resistance. You can unify
that you have some hairs outside Infosys at a
price of 12. You
want to shift from here to high growth IT
stocks like Tata Elxsi, if you have
entry commission ITS, then should you
unify here at 1665 and should you
enter these stocks, then is this
thing required? First of all,
if you want to enter Tata Elxsi here, if you
want to enter Anti IITS, then
you are going to a stock with a valuation more expensive than Infosys. There is
growth, but a lot of growth has already been factored in there.
This decision is due to the
anti-viral factor in Tata Elxsi.  There has been a
decline in BDO,
but no significant decline has been seen in Tata Elxsi yet,
so
I will not include that here. If
you have made up your mind here that you
want to know about growth by editing, then by
selling Infosys and partially selling LEDS,
I will make a good investment here.
Opposite is visible in its heart. We have already
established it and have made a video of it in the top
right corner. You have got the link, you
can watch the video. What is a good support?
You
can think about buying there.
Land Pharma is from Bangladesh, so the
level of 3000 is very important in Gland Pharma.
It went up by taking this support and here
it is trying to make a base around 3100 only.
So, its bike
price is seen on the chart from 3000 to around 3100. That is
pure fus regarding SLBM.
What is Updater Note Office Tehsil Bhim?
Album is Stock Lending and Borrowing.
Here we can do landing and
trading.
We can also look at the stocks we have in our demat account and
charge some fees for it.
Or if we
want to do pride, that can be done too.
What happens here is that a
position is created in stocks and then we have to give or take delivery. So, there is
no problem when
we have to give, if we don't have the stock, we have to
pay it or
we don't get some points. The future is trading
at a discount and the stock
price is going up. You
want to take advantage of this, so many people
talk over here and for that
you have the cylinders ready, they
need money, so you can land here. There is
not much risk in this because the
system is designed in such a way that there will
not be any major risk in the calendar. There is a scenario where whenever
borrowers pay a margin to
follow the stop, the margin is
around 125 percent in 125 days. Once
that margin has to be paid,  The remaining
hundred percent is recovered,
so a margin of twenty-five percent
remains. So, what happens many times is that if he
stays, he buys the staff again
from the margin, so you may
see short-term capital gains tax on the sale,
press this, the rest will go to your
city, you do
n't see any such thing here, from what time have you not seen it yet,
hey, your views on national, can it
fall again to 9811 and for the long term, the
test is good or Prince Pipe is good,
so see, there is a difference in additional principles,
astrology reading is a big company
and it is an electronic company, now a
school old company, a very old brand,
it is quite good, but in me, you
see the president SP, so along with
plastic products, that president
also works in it, so you
see the system a little more, so if you
need a little quick, you can think about staying with him, it will be
cheaper, he should be at the
entry level in the industry, let's
discuss about both,
capital can fall to 90 here, so
watch the festival here  The 90 level will first be
seen as a back support of 2000 levels.
Right now, it is 22 levels and
resistance to 2000 levels. So, as long as this level is there,
we cannot wait for 19 levels here. If it
goes below 2000, then the
levels of those areas can be seen. In fact, the
level of 800 levels can also be seen. If we
talk about the PIA industry,
then people will be able to see the entry level in the PIA industry. It is trading in a range.
So, those who are on the other side of it around 2017,
we can think about buying here, that is,
BCA, MCA and HDFC Life for the
long term. So, what should be done here? If
you have bought HDFC AMC on 25th, then
we have done a detailed discussion related to HDFC AMC.
If you have
not seen that video, you will find the link in the top right corner.
You can watch the video.
Talking about HDFC Life,
this red is trading at an important support level of
500 levels.  If seen, its
important level was around 550, but now a
decline has been seen. Now it should double fold at 510. If it
goes below this, then further
decline can be seen. So what
can you do? Now you fold here,
but if you want to average, then technically it is a little
strong, after that you
can think about buying. If a little
trend is seen and it goes above 600,
then you can think about buying here.
AA Solomon 99 is to be bought. Right now
you see a gap on the chart in profit, so should
you book profit? If you are a long
term investor, then you should not do all this. If you are a
short term investor, then of course you
can think about booking profit.
Instead, if there is a decline in panel exams,
then should you buy in the current market place?
You can see in Bajaj Finserv.
Currently, we see the stock trading in a channel, just
like NAFED
is doing, in the same way, it
is also trending in a channel, so on the lower side of
proximity, here you will
get around 13 thousand.  You can
think about buying there, it is a good
price, you are at a lower price, it is currently
trading at 15500, you may have to wait, but the
way the market conditions are,
Bajaj Finserv and the results are also not there, so
I would say to you, wait for the results,
you may not get good points
because most of the stocks have
seen a decline after the results, it is trading at a
raw level from the paper, so can you make a
long term investment
and Gold Gym International, Sudarshan Chemical, can we
invest for the long term, so if
you want to buy here, you can buy,
but hi re cholesterol
because it is a very small company, now let's
talk about Infosys, it is
trading at an important level,
around 20, many times we have seen the stock returning from here, it was
seen that now some support has
also been reached, if you want to buy then
according to me you should buy with a stop loss,
even if you are long term, what is its result, the
simple reason is that the stock is not such
that it did not do well, it performed very well
After that, we saw this stock
consolidating here and forming a base.
If this base breaks, then after
a long time, it could happen that the stock may go
down as well. There could be a
drop of 20-25% from here, or
you could see a big time correction.
What should be done in SBI Cards, ASI Technologies and Indiamart? If SBI
Cards gets or
goes above its resistance, then we can say that
if it comes around zero, then there
is a support here, we can think about buying. So if we
look at it now, it is
straight in the air. It would be
better if we do nothing right now. There is
definitely a small support around 10, but we cannot think of
selecting any big work there. It
comes at a good level, either it
goes above this, then we can work
or it is around this here, then we
can think about working.
Talking about HCL Tech, it appears to be at a good level,
Thousand Sixteen. It has
also been seen returning from here before with some
quantity.  One
can think about buying Indiamart because it is trading at a good level.
Talk about the weekly
chart in front of you. This is also good. Many
times I have told you here that the stock may
fall. When
no one was believing that the stock would go from 1000 to
5000, then we had told you that it could
go from 1000 to 5000. A decline was seen on the
technical side, but fundamentally the
company HDFC can perform well in the long term.
Do keep it on the police and
track it to see the company.
If we talk about it, it is trading in a range.
Technically, as long as it does not go above 5 minutes, there
should not be any downtrend and as long as it does
not go below 420, there
should not be much downtrend and it is
running at 42 but right now it is visible in the range,
so it becomes necessary to work according to both these levels.
Adani Port has been forced to medium.
In Adani Port, you can see that the
stock has reached its all-time high. It is a great stock and is a
good one.  It has been taken as such, nothing needs to be done right now, just
wait, the best spinner for you will be that we may
see a slight decline in it
or it may be seen for years, it will go
down a little further to 798, there is no doubt that we will
see a recovery after that,
trend a little here, which date should be done,
after that when the breakout happens then you
can buy here, your
probability of profit will be quite high, you will be
able to open with a small stop loss,
in the pharma sector you have Davis Loop
Dr Lal Path Lab planned for my friends,
which friends should I keep,
which one should I exit, see, all the
companies you see a little difference, they are
not exactly the same companies, so here if
you do not
want to invest in diagnostics here then you can invest in Lal Path Lab message, you can
remove it here, you
can invest accordingly, if you do not want to invest in small companies, you
can remove the lawless loop
and continue the beans and platform,
which bill to pay for exit,
always have to be selected here, it should not be done one time, it should be done
with one time stop loss
now  If this profit is made then we have done
all the accident once but if we are
thinking of selling, if we want to buy then we should
think about doing it, if it goes
above 500 then we can buy little by little and we
can complete it, we
should subscribe and have made a video to
talk about ICC's general insurance, for this 1200 level
is a very important level, now we will see, from here we got
to see Bigg Boss, the feel of it was also seen from here,
demand was seen from here, so
what should we do here right now, we should wait and watch,
now according to me it is
moving below the resistance and is also much
above the support, if it is found around the support then we
can think of buying, around
1250, around 1200 we can
attempt buying once
with stop loss and here if it goes
above the resistance which is approximately the
level of 4850 then we can buy,
adjacent to it or should fold for it,
20 types of such senior best midcaps
- tell me, so here see many such
midcap stocks  Airtel is a very good
stock, it is a very good source, the first
tranche is a very good stock, after that Relax is
also a very good stock, here we can
get feedback in place of Servi and
hate it, but positive should be
our focus to buy it here, these
subscribers also share very well,
this should be done well, we should
discuss about it, youth
can watch the video
that other Be Warn FD vs high price
bluechip like we have Nestle Page
Industry, if we want to invest for long term
then these blue chips will
give better returns in comparison to FD and the
quality will also be less and Dimple is the
advantage here, so what is
my view here that look, in blue chips,
according to me, in blue chips, these should be called blue chips from our Page Indore,
blue chip means
and you want low quality, hence I
recommend here that you should not use them
because they are still comparatively small,
when we
said that you should call only the market of more than one lakh crore,
all these are
companies of more than one lakh crore  If you
invest in it, you will get it and you will get it,
but instead of subscribing, I do
n't believe that investing in it is
not an investment, it becomes a
security, this is our emergency
fund, if something like this happens and it becomes
incumbent, then we
make a fund for it, so FD is necessary, right now it should be
kept in it and here our
goals are, we should see on a timely basis
that here is my 2 year solution,
so we will put the chemistry in it,
when it is invested in the stock, if it is invested for 2 years, then it
goes to FD 124,
if you are also investing for this year,
then should you invest in FD, no matter
how much you have, these are very much,
retirement is
also for the universe, but you have a goal which is a 20
year fund, after 20 years you will see,
then you need something, you want to buy something or if you have any
plan, then only you should invest in stocks, you can
invest as much time as you can, then go to the stock  You
should go into equity and its juice
because if time is with you
then the volatility will be settled and digested
and if you don't have time then you should take a
good shop right now, you might see a dead body there, so
instead of FD here, FD should
not be done with spoon change top, Shetty is also
necessary in his place,
Sudarshan Chemical on beta and Key's
International, I think the group is currently making
an arrangement, this is the weekly chart
and according to me the conditions are becoming true,
see here there is resistance, the fall continued, from
here the fall continued, but the
fall here recovered on Sambi and right now it is
also falling a little,
we seem to be trading around the resistance, so there
is a possibility here that we may see a breakfast, if it
goes above 2000 then we
can think about attending to buy, let's
talk about Sudarshan Chemical,
this is also the weekly chart and here currently the
stock is in the range of 500 to 600 2036  It
appears that there is resistance around 610 and
support around 500. If you
want to buy, you can buy with a small stop loss. You can
attend
because this level is very important even at 5. It may be for a
short time here,
but you may
see a rise. And the main thing is that
respiration is in your favor.
What should be done in today's international market? For
now, you can see that
we see a range of 370 to 430. So,
in this range, there is a plant operator. Earlier
also, it was seen in the arrangement. So
look here, even a little has happened
on the weekly chart because the structure
appears to be tied to us. So, the structure is
not good, but still we should attend. You
can think about attending with a little. If it becomes necessary for you to invest, then
we should click here. If you like it,